searchenabler.com 2013-05-04

# Privacy Policy of SEO Software and Analysis Platform | SearchEnabler

### SearchEnabler Privacy Policy

Last modified: 25 Feb, 2011

SearchEnabler.com is website of Quicko Technosoft Labs Private Limited.

We can be reached via e-mail at  or you can reach us via the contact page.

Our postal address is:  
#836, 27 Main,  
3 Cross, BTM 2nd Stage,  
Bangalore -76, India.

SearchEnabler is committed in protecting users privacy. SearchEnabler privacy policy governs the data collection and its usage. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us, by utilizing SearchEnabler services, you consent to the privacy-policy mentioned here within.

#### Collection and Usage of your Personal Information 

SearchEnabler collects and uses information voluntarily submitted by a user, such as a user’s name, email address, URLs and keywords, in connection with the services provided by SearchEnabler on behalf of such user.

SearchEnabler may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the SearchEnabler Site. This data is used to manage the SearchEnabler Site, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services. User IP addresses may also be recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

Billing information such as credit card details are not stored by SearchEnabler. Billing information is stored with partner, a secure payment gateway to provide a safe and secure payment procedure.

SearchEnabler uses collected information for products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. SearchEnabler may also use a user’s email address to send updates, such as a newsletter or news regarding SearchEnabler products and services. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by opting out.

SearchEnabler does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, who are performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SearchEnabler public message boards, blogs or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: SearchEnabler does not read your private online communications with others.<>

SearchEnabler websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SearchEnabler or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SearchEnabler (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SearchEnabler, or the public.

#### Usage of Tracking Information

SearchEnabler may use cookies or other similar tracking means to store user’s preferences and to record session information. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. They facilitate access to our website and personalize your online experience.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SearchEnabler services or websites you visit.

#### Links in SearchEnabler

The SearchEnabler Site may contain links to other sites. SearchEnabler is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the SearchEnabler Site.

#### Changes to privacy-policy

SearchEnabler from time to time update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SearchEnabler encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SearchEnabler is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the “Last Updated” date above.

#### Contacting SearchEnabler

If you have questions about this privacy policy, SearchEnabler practices or your dealings with SearchEnabler, Please contact us .
